<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet attribute="text/xsl" href="xofi.html.xslt"?>
<article xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
	xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
	xmlns="http://splitcells.net/sew.xsd"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://splitcells.net/sew.xsd sew.xsd">
	<meta>
		<title>Privacy Policy</title>
		<title_detailed>Privacy Policy (required by German law)
		</title_detailed>
		<description>This is the privacy policy of this site.</description>
		<related_to>
			<url>
				<site_instance_purl />
				/2015/03/04/about-this-site
			</url>
		</related_to>
		<publication_date year="2015" month="03"
			day_of_month="01" />
		<arbitrary_publication_date />
		<license>standard</license>
	</meta>
	<content>
		<paragraph>
			<link>
				<text>The generator provided by Law Offices of Weiß &amp; Partner
				</text>
				<url>https://www.ratgeberrecht.eu/leistungen/muster-datenschutzerklaerung.html
				</url>
			</link>
			was used for this privacy policy.
		</paragraph>
		<chapter>
			<title>Privacy Policy</title>
			<paragraph>
				Personal data (usually referred to just as
				<quote>data</quote>
				below)
				will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for
				the
				purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly website,
				including its contents, and the services offered there.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the
				General Data
				Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the
				<quote>GDPR</quote>
				), "processing" refers to any operation or set of operations
				such as
				collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage,
				adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by
				transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available,
				alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction
				performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in
				particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis
				for the processing of such data either under our own control or in
				conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the
				third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve
				the user experience which may result in said third parties also
				processing data they collect and control.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>Our privacy policy is structured as follows:</paragraph>
			<paragraph>I. Information about us as controllers of your data
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>II. The rights of users and data subjects</paragraph>
			<paragraph>III. Information about the data processing</paragraph>
			<chapter>
				<title>I. Information about us as controllers of your data</title>
				<tree>
					<name>
						The party responsible for this website (the
						<quote>controller</quote>
						)
						for purposes of data protection law is:
					</name>
					<tree>
						<name>Martins Avots</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>Buchengraben 4</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>Würzburg</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>Germany</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>mobile phone number: ***REMOVED***</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>Email: webmaster@splitcells.net</name>
					</tree>
				</tree>
			</chapter>
			<chapter>
				<title>II. The rights of users and data subjects</title>
				<tree>
					<name>With regard to the data processing to be described in more
						detail below, users and data subjects have the right:
					</name>
					<tree>
						<name>to confirmation of whether data concerning them is being
							processed, information about the data being processed, further
							information about the nature of the data processing, and copies
							of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);
						</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf.
							also Art. 16 GDPR);
						</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also
							Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is
							necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said
							processing per Art. 18 GDPR;
						</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or
							provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other
							providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);
						</name>
					</tree>
					<tree>
						<name>to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they
							believe that data concerning them is being processed by the
							controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art.
							77 GDPR).
						</name>
					</tree>
				</tree>
				<paragraph>In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all
					recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections,
					deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art.
					16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if
					such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate
					effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these
					recipients.
				</paragraph>
				<paragraph>
					<strong>Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have
						the right to object to the controller's future processing of their
						data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an
						objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising
						is permissible.
					</strong>
				</paragraph>
			</chapter>
			<chapter>
				<title>III. Information about the data processing</title>
				<paragraph>Your data processed when using our website will be
					deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to
					apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any
					statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.
				</paragraph>
				<chapter>
					<title>Server data</title>
					<paragraph>For technical reasons, the following data sent by your
						internet browser to us or to our server provider will be
						collected, especially to ensure a secure and stable website: These
						server log files record the type and version of your browser,
						operating system, the website from which you came (referrer URL),
						the webpages on our site visited, the date and time of your visit,
						as well as the IP address from which you visited our site.
					</paragraph>
					<paragraph>The data thus collected will be temporarily stored, but
						not in association with any other of your data.
					</paragraph>
					<paragraph>The basis for this storage is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f)
						GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the improvement, stability,
						functionality, and security of our website.
					</paragraph>
					<paragraph>The data will be deleted within no more than seven days,
						unless continued storage is required for evidentiary purposes. In
						which case, all or part of the data will be excluded from deletion
						until the investigation of the relevant incident is finally
						resolved.
					</paragraph>
				</chapter>
				<chapter>
					<title>Contact</title>
					<paragraph>If you contact us via email or the contact form, the
						data you provide will be used for the purpose of processing your
						request. We must have this data in order to process and answer
						your inquiry; otherwise we will not be able to answer it in full
						or at all.
					</paragraph>
					<paragraph>The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 Para.
						1 lit. b) GDPR.
					</paragraph>
					<paragraph>Your data will be deleted once we have fully answered
						your inquiry and there is no further legal obligation to store
						your data, such as if an order or contract resulted therefrom.
					</paragraph>
				</chapter>
			</chapter>
			<paragraph>
				<link>
					<text>Model Data Protection Statement</text>
					<url>https://www.ratgeberrecht.eu/leistungen/muster-datenschutzerklaerung.html
					</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<text>Anwaltskanzlei Weiß &amp; Partner</text>
					<url>https://www.ratgeberrecht.eu/</url>
				</link>
			</paragraph>
		</chapter>
	</content>
</article>